/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data10_1', {
    title: '10.1 Adding Unlike Fractions',
    path: '10.1-adding-unlike-fractions',
    children: [{
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{17}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{20}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{12}}{\\fracstr{20}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{17}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{9}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{36}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{9}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{36}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{36}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{36}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{13}}{\\input{36}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{2}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{10}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{2}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{4}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{10}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\input{10}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{2}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{9}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{12}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{11}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{8}}{\\str{7}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{52}}{\\input{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{7}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{21}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{8}}{\\fracstr{7}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{21}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{28}}{\\fracstr{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{24}}{\\fracstr{21}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{28}}{\\fracstr{21}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{52}}{\\input{21}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{15}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{107}}{\\input{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{15}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{120}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{15}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{75}}{\\fracstr{120}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{32}}{\\fracstr{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{75}}{\\fracstr{120}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{32}}{\\fracstr{120}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{107}}{\\input{120}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{8}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{65}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\str{\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{24}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{15}}{\\fracstr{8}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{45}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{45}}{\\fracstr{24}}}{\\row{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{20}}{\\fracstr{24}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{65}}{\\input{24}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{2}}{\\fracstr{5}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{3}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{60}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{2}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{24}}{\\fracstr{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{20}}{\\fracstr{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{24}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{20}}{\\str{60}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{49}}{\\input{60}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{27}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{3}}{\\fracstr{10}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{1}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{4}}{\\fracstr{5}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{20}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{3}}{\\str{10}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{1}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{4}}{\\str{5}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{6}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{5}}{\\fracstr{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{16}}{\\fracstr{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{6}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{16}}{\\str{20}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{27}}{\\input{20}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Adding Unlike Fractions',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{57}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false,
                    "workbook": true
                }
            }]
        }, {
            title: 'Workbook',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Find the lowest common denominator (LCD) of the fractions:}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{5}}{\\fracstr{4}}}{\\row{\\str{, \xA0}}}{\\row{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{3}}}{\\row{\\str{,\xA0 and \xA0}}}{\\frac{\\fracstr{7}}{\\fracstr{6}}}}',
                answer: '\\input{12}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                },
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Use the LCD to convert the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{5}}{\\str{4}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{3}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{7}}{\\str{6}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\grp{\\frac{\\input{15}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{28}}{\\fracstr{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\input{14}}{\\fracstr{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }, {
                problem: '\\rowgrp{\\row{\\str{Add the fractions: }}}{\\row{\\frac{\\str{15}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{28}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 + \xA0}}{\\frac{\\str{14}}{\\str{12}}}{\\sign{\xA0 \xA0 = \xA0}}}}',
                answer: '\\row{\\frac{\\input{57}}{\\input{12}}}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": false
                }
            }]
        }]
    }]
});
